Please subscribe to my channel!
I'm going to close the door.
Thank you for watching.
It's the day of the show.
Did you sleep well?
Yes, I did.
I slept for 9 and a half hours.
Oh, same as me.
It's perfect.
I'll do my best.
When I was in the first place of Tokyo
Invasion, I had few days to rehearse.
And I was impatient.
But this time, I had a lot of
rehearsals, so I can relax.
I've said it many times, but I've been
to Tokyo Dome City Hall once.
I'm glad I can perform there.
I have to watch it carefully.
I'm TOTAKU.
Thank you for waiting.
Please have a meal.
Thank you.
It's under 5 seconds.
Please eat it.
It's delicious.
It's so crispy.
It's as crispy as a laser.
Please subscribe to this channel.
What?
Good bye.
Thank you.
We are waiting for you.
Yes, we are.
Thank you.
I will practice soon.
I'm nervous.
Thank you.
When we perform at festivals, we
usually sing high notes.
So we usually sing high notes.
But we don't sing high notes in big
shows.
We sing low notes, sing high notes, and
sing low notes.
People might think we are singing high
notes.
But we are not.
We are not singing high notes.
We don't sing high notes in big shows.
We also sing low notes.
So we are not singing high notes in big
shows.
But we want people to feel our
technical skills.
We want to improve our skills.
Are you ready?
Yes.
Let's go.
Don't touch.
I'm nervous because we are performing
at midnight.
Right, Kanae?
Yes.
Help me.
We have been practicing for a long
time.
We have been singing and dancing.
We both have a hard time.
Let's do our best.
I'm nervous.
It's not a wave roll.
I got a strawberry.
I want to do this.
I see.
Oh, no.
I'm going to get lost.
I'll make a prediction.
Let's go to the microphone.
This way.
You can't go this way.
I'm going to go this way.
KOBE
The first day of the concert
The second day of the concert
The third day of the concert
The concert hall
Pardon me.
Can you please raise your flag?
It has been fixed.
Thank you for watching!
In the meantime, I finished capturing
cute children.
Thank you for watching!
We just finished the rehearsal.
The sound was good.
I'm not nervous than the last time.
I was very excited when the over-
choreography of the rehearsal started.
I thought I wasn't nervous, but I was
nervous.
I'm looking forward to the tension.
Thank you for your hard work.
Is there anything?
Everyone, everyone, everyone.
Thank you for your hard work.
Is it okay to say that loud?
I have about 10 things to do, so I'll
do it.
It's all clear.
It's clear.
I'll do my best to live tomorrow.
I don't know what tomorrow will be
like.
I'll do my best to live tomorrow.
What?
I'm going to do my best today.
Don't look at me.
I'm not looking.
I'm nervous.
What is the word to relieve tension?
Thank you for watching.
It's manga that I recommend for playing
jumps.
Hahaha he's right.
Omyou chan and Nijimi-chan x Toko-chan
Bye bye!
We're going to go!
Let's take a picture together.
Yes.
Thank you.
We're going to go!
Great!
Which way are we going?
Can we sing together?
Can we sing?
I want to sing!
OK!
Please take it!
Yes!
We can't lose to the one-way ticket!
Fight! Fight!
I'll show you how to get it!
No matter how many times you fall, you
can't give up!
More! More! More! More!
Aim higher!
It's a sudden!
It's a sudden debut!
OK!
Oh, I see.
Like when we practice.
Please say, enjoy.
It's fun to stand on the stage.
We never switch when we're on the
stage.
Let's have fun!
Who?
Hine
Mio
Shinju
Waka
Kaya
Kaya!
Hine Mio Shinju Waka Kaya!
Please.
Bye bye.
It's a battle of who can enjoy it.
Let's do our best.
It's okay.
Yes.
Thank you.
Bye bye.
Where is the microphone?
Swi神-46
Sw wiers songs
Thank you!
I'm going to fall in love with you a
little more.
I love you!
Take a break.
We are Horanger dash 1.
Team Musume.
Mizari.
Akari.
Natsuki.
Natsuki Rukia.
Taka.
Mizuki.
relaxing dance.
To be honest,
I don't know if we're making progress
or not.
You know, We always do.
But.
If we're in a large hall like this,
we were able experience a lot of
skaters' play
coming here and watching us live.
Looking at the scenery it was...
I don't know what it was but
I don't know if a step ahead of our
course
As always downtown
hola,hola
From nowhere to yutake
Find a diamond!
Come on!
Do your best!
I know you believe me, please
Let's go to the next place, please
Finally, let's go
Please
Everyone, one, two, please
Don't stop, don't stop, you don't stop
I want to make it come true
I'll get in the trophy right away
You can do it with the camera
I can see your heart
I can see that
Let's go
Oh, sorry
Thank you for your support
Thank you!
Takemone!
I fell down at the back of the line.
I'm a little injured.
I'm taking the second place now.
I can't get out of here.
I don't have any injuries.
I'm feeling very well.
I'm a little injured.
I'm taking the second place for the
future.
Please wait a little longer for me to
recover.
I'll be performing with nine people's
feelings.
Are you ready to cheer for me?
I'm going to start the performance.
I'll be fine if I'm with you
Even if we meet again
If we're separated, we'll meet again
So let's be together
Forever
Thank you very much!
Kai, Chiyu!
One more time!
Ready, Kai, Chiyu!
Thank you very much!
That's all!
We are Mizutamari Bond!
Thank you for watching!
Please subscribe to our channel!